Good evening, have a good week.
Happy birthday to the ILF,
Israeli Leadership Forum.
Today we have 500 members,
a powerful community bringing
leaders together
out of a true desire to create change.
Thank you very much, dear members
of the ILF. I'm glad to be a part of ILF.
There is an inconceivable power here,
a power of people.
A much larger power
than we each have as individuals.
And it's really exciting to see
that the values
are the guiding light for everyone
sitting in this room,
in order to change the world.
We sit looking at a new immigrant
who just came here three years ago,
making change, dramatic change.
He represents the Israel
we don't see on the news.
The normal Israel.
Man of the Year in Israel,
Silvan Adams.
So believe it or not,
because they suspect us,
I'd say,
because of the news reports from over here,
we need always show
the best face of Israel.